<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView Recipes</string>

    <string-array name="recipe_names">
        <item>Chorizo Breakfast Tacos with Potato Hash and Eggs</item>
        <item>Baked French Toast</item>
        <item>French Toast Casserole</item>
        <item>Banana Bread</item>
        <item>Quick Quiche</item>
        <item>Truck-Stop Buttermilk Pancakes</item>
        <item>Vegan Pancakes</item>
        <item>Baked Ham and Cheese Party Sandwiches</item>
        <item>Easy Sausage Gravy and Biscuits</item>
        <item>Spinach Quiche</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_descriptions">
        <item>Chorizo breakfast tacos with potato hash and eggs are ridiculously flavorful, quick,
            and easy. The perfect meal any time of day!</item>
        <item>I got this recipe from my sister in law. She and my brother had it at their gift
            opening after the wedding. I make it any time we have people staying with us, and it is
            always a hit. You may sprinkle the top with pecans if you wish.</item>
        <item>Tastes good for breakfast, just like French toast. It\'s easy to make too! Serve warm
            with maple syrup on top.</item>
        <item>This is our family favorite.</item>
        <item>When you don\'t have the time to make a pastry crust, try this quick lunch idea. You
            may add any other goodies you like, such as ham, chicken, crab, shrimp or broccoli.</item>
        <item>A yummy breakfast treat, and very easy to make!! Serve with bacon or sausage, and
            some fried eggs, wonderful!!! Batter will keep in fridge for a couple of days if you
            can\'t make all at once, or you can freeze and make at a later date.</item>
        <item>This batter makes light, fluffy, and delicious pancakes. I have been making them for
            years and everyone that tries them wants the recipe.</item>
        <item>These small, delicious sandwiches are perfect for any party. They are so good that
            even the pickiest of eaters will eat these.</item>
        <item>Hot jumbo buttermilk biscuits with creamy sausage gravy are ready in just 15 minutes
            for a hearty, family-favorite breakfast.</item>
        <item>I don\'t normally like cooked spinach but I fell in love with this at first bite.
            Sooo good!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_details">
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            2 tablespoons vegetable oil \n
            2 baked potatoes, peeled and cubed \n
            1/2 cup chopped onion \n
            1/2 teaspoon garlic powder \n
            1/2 teaspoon onion powder \n
            salt and freshly ground black pepper \n
            7 ounces chorizo sausage, removed from casings \n
            5 eggs \n
            1 tablespoon milk \n
            3 tablespoons finely chopped fresh cilantro, divided \n
            6 small corn tortillas, warmed \n
            1/2 cup shredded Cheddar cheese \n
            6 tablespoons salsa \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Heat oil in a nonstick skillet over medium-high heat until shimmering. Add potatoes,
            onion, garlic powder, and onion powder to one side of the skillet and season with salt
            and pepper. Add chorizo sausage on the other side of the skillet and saute, breaking up
            with the back of a spoon, until browned, about 5 minutes. Turn over the potatoes after a
            couple of minutes so they get brown on both sides. \n\n

            2. Combine eggs, milk, 1 tablespoon cilantro, salt, and pepper in a bowl. Reduce heat and
            pour egg mixture into the skillet. Stir eggs until they are very softly set, about
            3 minutes. Remove from heat. \n\n

            3. Spread out warmed tortillas and divide potato, chorizo, and egg mixture among them.
            Sprinkle with remaining 2 tablespoons cilantro. Top with Cheddar cheese and salsa. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            1 (1 pound) loaf French bread, cut diagonally in 1 inch slices \n
            8 eggs \n
            2 cups milk \n
            1 1/2 cups half-and-half cream \n
            2 teaspoons vanilla extract \n
            1/4 teaspoon ground cinnamon \n
            3/4 cup butter \n
            1 1/3 cups brown sugar \n
            3 tablespoons light corn syrup \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Butter a 9x13 inch baking dish. Arrange the slices of bread in the bottom. In a large
            bowl, beat together eggs, milk, cream, vanilla and cinnamon. Pour over bread slices,
            cover, and refrigerate overnight. \n\n

            2. The next morning, preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). In a small saucepan,
            combine butter, brown sugar and corn syrup; heat until bubbling. Pour over bread and egg
            mixture. \n\n

            3. Bake in preheated oven, uncovered, for 40 minutes. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            5 cups bread cubes \n
            4 eggs \n
            1 1/2 cups milk \n
            1/4 cup white sugar, divided \n
            1/4 teaspoon salt \n
            1 teaspoon vanilla extract \n
            1 tablespoon margarine, softened \n
            1 teaspoon ground cinnamon \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Lightly butter an 8x8 inch baking pan. \n\n

            2. Line bottom of pan with bread cubes. In a large bowl, beat together eggs, milk, 2
            tablespoons sugar, salt and vanilla. pour egg mixture over bread. Dot with margarine;
            let stand for 10 minutes. \n\n

            3. Combine remaining 2 tablespoons sugar with 1 teaspoon cinnamon and sprinkle over the
            top. Bake in preheated oven about 45 to 50 minutes, until top is golden. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            1 1/2 cups all-purpose flour \n
            1 teaspoon baking soda \n
            1/2 teaspoon salt \n
            1 cup white sugar \n
            2 eggs, beaten \n
            1/4 cup butter, melted \n
            3 bananas, mashed \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Grease and flour two 7x3 inch loaf pans. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). \n\n

            2. In one bowl, whisk together flour, soda, salt, and sugar. Mix in slightly beaten eggs,
            melted butter, and mashed bananas. Stir in nuts if desired. Pour into prepared pans. \n\n

            3. Bake at 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 1 hour, or until a wooden toothpick inserted
            in the center comes out clean. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            8 slices bacon \n
            4 ounces shredded Swiss cheese \n
            2 tablespoons butter, melted \n
            4 eggs, beaten \n
            1/4 cup finely chopped onion \n
            1 teaspoon salt \n
            1/2 cup all-purpose flour \n
            1 1/2 cups milk \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Place bacon in a large, deep skillet. Cook over medium high heat until evenly brown.
            Drain, crumble and set aside. \n\n

            2. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Lightly grease a 9 inch pie pan. \n\n

            3. Line bottom of pie plate with cheese and crumbled bacon. Combine eggs, butter, onion,
            salt, flour and milk; whisk together until smooth; pour into pie pan. \n\n

            4. Bake in preheated oven for 35 minutes, until set. Serve hot or cold. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            5 eggs \n
            1 1/2 cups milk \n
            6 tablespoons butter, melted \n
            5 cups buttermilk \n
            5 cups all-purpose flour \n
            5 teaspoons baking powder \n
            5 teaspoons baking soda \n
            1 pinch salt (optional) \n
            5 tablespoons sugar \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. In a large bowl, whisk together the eggs, milk, butter and buttermilk. Combine the
            flour, baking powder, baking soda and sugar; stir into the wet ingredients just until
            blended. Adjust the thickness of the batter to your liking by adding more flour or
            buttermilk if necessary. \n\n

            2. Heat a large skillet over medium heat, and coat with cooking spray. Pour 1/4 cupfuls of
            batter onto the skillet, and cook until bubbles appear on the surface. Flip with a
            spatula, and cook until browned on the other side. Continue with remaining batter. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            1 1/4 cups all-purpose flour \n
            2 tablespoons white sugar \n
            2 teaspoons baking powder \n
            1/2 teaspoon salt \n
            1 1/4 cups water \n
            1 tablespoon oil \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Sift the flour, sugar, baking powder, and salt into a large bowl. Whisk the water and
            oil together in a small bowl. Make a well in the center of the dry ingredients, and pour
            in the wet. Stir just until blended; mixture will be lumpy. \n\n

            2. Heat a lightly oiled griddle over medium-high heat. Drop batter by large spoonfuls onto
            the griddle, and cook until bubbles form and the edges are dry. Flip, and cook until
            browned on the other side. Repeat with remaining batter. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            3/4 cup melted butter \n
            1 1/2 tablespoons Dijon mustard \n
            1 1/2 teaspoons Worcestershire sauce \n
            1 1/2 tablespoons poppy seeds \n
            1 tablespoon dried minced onion \n
            24 mini sandwich rolls \n
            1 pound thinly sliced cooked deli ham \n
            1 pound thinly sliced Swiss cheese \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease a 9x13-inch baking dish. \n\n

            2. In a bowl, mix together butter, Dijon mustard, Worcestershire sauce, poppy seeds, and
            dried onion. Separate the tops from bottoms of the rolls, and place the bottom pieces
            into the prepared baking dish. Layer about half the ham onto the rolls. Arrange the
            Swiss cheese over the ham, and top with remaining ham slices in a layer. Place the tops
            of the rolls onto the sandwiches. Pour the mustard mixture evenly over the rolls. \n\n

            3. Bake in the preheated oven until the rolls are lightly browned and the cheese has melted,
            about 20 minutes. Slice into individual rolls through the ham and cheese layers to serve. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            1 (16 ounce) can refrigerated jumbo buttermilk biscuits \n
            1 (9.6 ounce) package Jimmy Dean® Original Hearty Pork Sausage Crumbles \n
            1/4 cup flour \n
            2 1/2 cups milk \n
            Salt and ground black pepper to taste \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Bake biscuits according to package directions. \n\n

            2. Meanwhile, cook sausage in large skillet over medium heat 5-6 minutes or until
            thoroughly heated, stirring frequently. Stir in flour. Gradually add milk; cook until
            mixture comes to a boil and thickens, stirring constantly. Reduce heat to medium-low;
            simmer 2 minutes, stirring constantly. Season to taste with salt and pepper. \n\n

            3. Split biscuits in half. Place 2 halves on each of 8 plates; top with about 1/3 cup gravy. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            <b>Ingredients</b> \n 
            1 (10 ounce) package frozen chopped spinach, thawed \n
            1 bunch green onions, finely chopped (white parts only) \n
            4 eggs, beaten \n
            1 (16 ounce) package cottage cheese \n
            2 cups shredded Cheddar cheese \n
            1/4 cup crushed croutons \n\n

            <b>Directions</b> \n 
            1. Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C). Lightly grease a 9 inch pie or quiche pan. \n\n

            2. Place spinach in a small saucepan. Cook over medium heat, stirring occasionally until
            soft. Drain off any remaining liquid. Stir in green onions, eggs, cottage cheese and
            Cheddar cheese. Pour mixture into prepared pan. \n\n

            3. Bake uncovered in preheated oven for 45 minutes. Remove from oven and sprinkle with
            crushed croutons. Return to oven and bake for an additional 15 minutes, until eggs are
            set. \n\n
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_images">
        <item>chorizo</item>
        <item>baked_french_toast</item>
        <item>french_toast_casserole</item>
        <item>banana_bread</item>
        <item>quick_quiche</item>
        <item>buttermilk_pancakes</item>
        <item>vegan_pancakes</item>
        <item>baked_ham_and_cheese</item>
        <item>easy_sausage_gravy_and_biscuits</item>
        <item>spinach_quiche</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
